(Howard:)Hi. Howard Wolowitz.
Oh. Issabella Concepcion.
(Howard:)Oh, yeah, the astronomer.
(Howard:)Raj told us
about you.
Hey! Free toilet paper!
(Isabella:)You told him
I was an astronomer?
(Cleaner:)Uh...
(Sheldon:)I understand.
(Raj:)Time to go.
No, p-please don't.
(Isabella:)It's okay, Rajesh,
I'm a grown woman.
(Isabella:)I don't have to waste my time
(Sheldon:)with someone
who's embarrassed by me.
(Howard:)I can keep this, right?
Issabella!
Issabella, wait,
wait, let me explain.
(Isabella:)If you are embarrassed
by what I do,
(Isabella:)why did you pursue me?
I'm sorry.
Honestly, I-I didn't think
your job would bother me,
(Raj:)but I guess it did.
(Raj:)And I hate myself for that.
(Raj:)But there's
a lot of things
(Raj:)about me that would
totally embarrass you.
(Isabella:)I doubt that.
(Raj:)Well, prepare to be mortified.
(Raj:)I let my dog eat food out
of my mouth,
(Raj:)not because she likes it
but because I do.
(Raj:)Also, I know they're pretty,
but I'm scared of butterflies.